<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Donut-Mod – For Developers</title><link>/docs/contribution-guidelines/</link><description>Recent content in For Developers on Donut-Mod</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/docs/contribution-guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Docs: Future Improvements</title><link>/docs/contribution-guidelines/future_improvements/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/contribution-guidelines/future_improvements/</guid><description>
&lt;p>If you are looking to add to the project, or simply want to describe missing features, working with us is most easily done through GitHub.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To discuss an issue, or something missing, adding a GitHub issue &lt;a href="https://github.com/Donut-Mod-Team/donut-mod/issues">here&lt;/a> will peak our interest, and we will get back to you as soon as possible.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As for contributing to the project yourself, forking the repository and adding a pull request will allow us to review what you have done, and discuss it internally within the team.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Docs: Technical</title><link>/docs/contribution-guidelines/technical/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/contribution-guidelines/technical/</guid><description>
&lt;p>To work with the project and set up a development server, you will need to &lt;a href="https://tibcosoftware.github.io/spotfire-mods/docs/getting-started/">follow this guide&lt;/a> provided by Tibco for working with mods.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You will need, as described in the aforementioned guide, to have Node.js installed, a code editor, and a working instance of Spotfire®. The mod is functional with all browsers that can run the browser version of Spotfire®.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Forking the project to work with it locally will provide to be the most efficient if you wish to contribute to the main project, or simply work with the mod for yourself, which is also discussed in the Future Improvements section in this subsection of the docs.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>